[{"answer": "Not even close.", "docId": "120404pmt", "aSentId": 29, "question": "What does Nugent want?", "qSentId": 28}, {"answer": "What I want is the Second Amendment.", "docId": "120404pmt", "aSentId": 31, "question": "What do you want?", "qSentId": 30}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, there's no warrant for him to be arrested.", "docId": "120404pmt", "aSentId": 45, "question": "Do you believe that it might be in your client's best interest now if he was to turn himself in?", "qSentId": 44}, {"answer": "George Zimmerman was on his way to the store, and he was allowed to legally carry a gun with him because he had a concealed weapons permit when he went to the store that night.", "docId": "120404pmt", "aSentId": 72, "question": "Would you accept that as a fact?", "qSentId": 71}, {"answer": "The one thing we know as a fact is that George Zimmerman was attacked by Trayvon Martin.", "docId": "120404pmt", "aSentId": 74, "question": "But if he was acting as a neighborhood watch official, then you would accept as a fact that he should not have been carrying a weapon, or, indeed, using it?", "qSentId": 73}, {"answer": "No, they did not.", "docId": "120404pmt", "aSentId": 104, "question": "Do you accept that as a fact?", "qSentId": 103}, {"answer": "I'll accept that he was acting as a responsible citizen who happened to be the one that the newsletter for that community says, if you see something suspicious, called George Zimmerman.", "docId": "120404pmt", "aSentId": 132, "question": "Is that what you're saying?", "qSentId": 131}, {"answer": "You are wrong.", "docId": "120404pmt", "aSentId": 142, "question": "That is the law, isn't it?", "qSentId": 141}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "120404pmt", "aSentId": 150, "question": "They can all go up with firearms, can they?", "qSentId": 149}, {"answer": "I can state as a fact that his nose is broken.", "docId": "120404pmt", "aSentId": 202, "question": "But you can state as a fact that his nose is broken?", "qSentId": 201}, {"answer": "That's right.", "docId": "120404pmt", "aSentId": 236, "question": "How could it be in the police report that he'd gone to buy Skittles?", "qSentId": 235}, {"answer": "I do, do.", "docId": "120404pmt", "aSentId": 244, "question": "If there are some questions about American jurisprudence or something like that?", "qSentId": 243}, {"answer": "Sir, I will tell you there is evidence that will come out in a court of law, that will be admissible that will show this.", "docId": "120404pmt", "aSentId": 265, "question": "As far as I'm aware, there is no eyewitness that has seen Trayvon Martin, an eyewitness that saw Trayvon Martin land the first blow, is there?", "qSentId": 264}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120404pmt", "aSentId": 279, "question": "And my final question, can be both of you, do you expect George Zimmerman to be arrested imminently?", "qSentId": 278}, {"answer": "I would say certainly not in the next few days.", "docId": "120404pmt", "aSentId": 283, "question": "In the next few days, next couple of weeks?", "qSentId": 282}, {"answer": "If the grand jury hears all the evidence that we know to exist and they apply the law as it exists in Florida, not Great Britain, then he will not be arrested in the next few days or the next few weeks or ever.", "docId": "120404pmt", "aSentId": 286, "question": "But is there anyone expectation that at some stage George Zimmerman will be arrested on your side?", "qSentId": 285}, {"answer": "Well, obviously, they did not want to look at the facts that have been released by the police department, the fact that it is highly unusual that someone can kill someone in cold blood and that person not be armed and George Zimmerman has a .9 millimeter gun.", "docId": "120404pmt", "aSentId": 310, "question": "When you listened to what they said, what was your reaction?", "qSentId": 309}, {"answer": "Well, I don't think we can say attacked.", "docId": "120404pmt", "aSentId": 345, "question": "Could it be that he did attack and jump on George Zimmerman?", "qSentId": 344}, {"answer": "Certainly that's what he wants to assert.", "docId": "120404pmt", "aSentId": 371, "question": "Can you accept that that could be a possibility?", "qSentId": 370}, {"answer": "ORGAN: Mr. Crump, I'm going to have to leave it there.", "docId": "120404pmt", "aSentId": 400, "question": "Would Trayvon Martin be given all this consideration had he been the trigger man?", "qSentId": 399}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, thanks for going after this very tragic situation, Piers.", "docId": "120404pmt", "aSentId": 425, "question": "What do you make of this case in its entirety?", "qSentId": 424}, {"answer": "You saw the tape.", "docId": "120404pmt", "aSentId": 444, "question": "Even for someone like you, that believes in right to bear arms and guns and everything else, shouldn't he have been arrested?", "qSentId": 443}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120404pmt", "aSentId": 495, "question": "But do you believe that a neighborhood watch official acting in that capacity should be armed and using that firearm?", "qSentId": 494}, {"answer": "Well, I think it comes down to one word, which is race.", "docId": "120404pmt", "aSentId": 512, "question": "What is your view of it?", "qSentId": 511}, {"answer": "Well, I think we're stuck in a box doing the same thing over and over every single day.", "docId": "120404pmt", "aSentId": 528, "question": "What do you believe has gone fundamentally wrong with the American business model?", "qSentId": 527}, {"answer": "Well, we don't really know how to do that.", "docId": "120404pmt", "aSentId": 546, "question": "The premise of your book, \"The Passport to Success,\" do you believe that enough Americans take personal responsibility these days for their lives, for their careers, for their economic stability and so on?", "qSentId": 545}]